## **VEDHAPRIYA RAJAGOPAL**

+ 1 201-294-7979 | vedhapriya05@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Meticulous Software Engineer with 2 years of experience in designing, testing, and developing software solutions. In-depth understanding of web technologies with focus on delivering innovative business solutions. Excels in a fast-paced, high-energy, and deadline-driven environment with willingness to take on additional tasks.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React JS
- JSON

- Redux
- TypeScript
- Node.JS, Express
- MongoDB, SQL
- REST API

- Bootstrap, Material Design
- GIT/GIT Hub version control

# **EXPERIENCE**

Per Scholas | Software Engineering | Aug-Nov 2022 (with Full-time Parenting) | 2012-Present

- Developed Full Stack Web Applications including Service Request Management, Weather App, E-Commerce Website using full stack (MERN) and RESTful web services.
- Designed and developed Property Management System with enhanced navigation for best user experience with secured Authentication system with SDLC design process
- Knowledge in working with Redux architecture to implement complex state management.

Soft Skills: Enhanced my creativity with my artistic works. Planning, organizing and managing time are key things for raising successful family.

Computer Science Corporation (CSC) | Associate Software Engineer | 2010-2012

- Analyzed business requirements and formulated testing approaches. Prepared and implemented test scripts and test plans. Developed task for UI functionality and content testing.
- In addition, played a key role in the support team in handling tickets effectively and provide troubleshooting with patient step-by-step instructions to resolve problems.

### **EDUCATION**

- Bachelor of Technology Information Technology | 2006-2010
  Velammal Engineering College, Anna University, India
- Software Engineering Training | Aug-Nov 2022 | PerScholas, Newark, New Jersey